Hi, kids.
嗨  孩子们
Hey, mom.
嘿  妈妈
Come on, Charlie, let's go see daddy.
走吧  Charlie  我们去找爸爸
You know what I realized today?
你知道我今天发现什么了吗
Charlie's never played laser tag.
Charlie还从来没玩过激光枪大战呢
I bet she'd enjoy doing that on Friday night.
我赌她星期五晚上一定会玩得很开心的
Oh, how very sweet and unselfish of you.
噢  你真是体贴又无私啊
But Charlie's gonna be with us Friday night.
但是Charlie星期五晚上要和我们呆在一起
It's your school's open house.
去参加你学校的家长会
Right. Forgot about that.
啊是啊  我都忘了这一茬儿了
Well, we haven't.
我们可不会忘
Dad and I can't wait to meet this miracle worker--Mrs. Mellish.
我和你爸都等不及想去见见这位神奇的Mellish老师
She's the first teacher who hasn't called to complain about you.
她是第一个没有打电话向我告你的状的老师
Are you sure he's actually going to school?
你确定他真的去上过学吗